It's been a while!
Hoxy's back!
Thank you for having me again!
Glad to be here!
Nice to see you again!
I've planned something special for you today!
You've never worn silicone before, right?
That's right, yeah!
So I'm going to put you on a silicone cat seat today!
Everything you told me about is super funny!
I'm kind of curious, yeah!
Let's see!
You're strong, you're prepared to lift some weight!
For sure I am!
The silicone catsuit is like 4kg.
Yeah, it's like two bottles of beer.
Two bottles of beer?
Four or five.
Depends on the beer.
Oh wow.
Oh well.
The black one.
Yeah.
That's sticky.
Oh wow.
So, first impression.
It's quite nice.
It's quite heavy, so you're right.
It's kind of squishy.
And the first time in my life I'm not afraid to destroy anything with my picky nails.
Yes.
It seems to be quite tough.
You have to watch out for your hair.
Because hair sticks to it.
And we have some pretty formed boobs basically.
So you're ready to try it on?
I am.
And we'll have to lube you up.
Alright, I'm gonna put this down and you're probably going to want to sit in the chair.
Sit? Okay.
Because I'm going to hand you the lube, it's water-based lube.
So, yeah, you should start to lube yourself.
Yeah, you can help me with the other one.
With the other one, with the other leg?
Yeah.
Alright.
Oh, wow.
And yes, she's wearing a bodysuit because we are on YouTube and it's not new porn so
Yeah, better safe than sorry
How does it feel?
I'm feeling super looped at the moment
Yeah
Okay, so it is it is a neck entry catsuit so you have to dress it basically like you would do
with a
latex neck entry catsuit
Like you take this and then try to put your foot inside.
How? Look at this little, super little...
It's really whole, like it's really really stretchy.
Stretchy, again.
I don't think that my whole body gonna fit in there.
It does, I've worn it too and it will.
Are you sure about it?
Yeah.
You have to find the right leg.
And I just pull it up like a tight. Yeah, it's like there you go
That's why I looped your feet
It can feel super funny like yeah, so next like
I already got hair down there. Yeah, don't worry about that
You should help me
Well, is this the leg?
Ah!
Tada!
It feels like work.
Yeah.
Do you think I moved enough?
I don't know.
How do you feel?
Do you feel squishy and...
I feel squishy...
...slidy...
...or whatever.
I'm so kind of afraid of my nails.
It's 4mm thick so you should be fine.
Yeah, it's better.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Yeah, here we go.
Super squishy.
Yeah.
Feels like a marshmallow.
I kind of love it.
Yeah.
Feels like a marshmallow.
Kinda love it.
Alright, do you feel like the bottom part is in place where it should be?
The bottom part?
Yeah.
Do you need to put more from the legs?
Yeah, a bit.
That's a good thing about silicone, you can simply pull it up, not as with latex.
That's cool.
So here we are.
So let me pull the arm away and you're going to slip inside the arm.
How?
Because you're looped up.
Oh well.
Yeah.
That kind of works.
Okay.
Oh, wow.
Well, yeah.
Alright, here you go.
There you go.
Oh, the air.
Yeah.
Alright.
the moment I'm in it's not that heavy it's not that heavy you will feel it in your shoulders
at some point that's what I reckon when I'm wearing it for longer than a few minutes okay
we'll see but it does fit you it feels great so far so we do have some shiner this is the
Futura X shiner and I'm going to shine you. So this is size medium there is
large and extra large available and a lot of other products you should check out the
Futura X homepage. You can wear matte of course but if you shine it up it's
really really shiny. It looks like latex but it doesn't have the seams.
I love the the shiny look so thank you for shining up for me.
I can feel it that it's thicker than latex yeah so I don't feel the the touch
of your so much of my skin. Yeah so it's more like there's more of a barrier. Yeah.
It's four millimeter thick. Yeah. Ta-da! You're done dressing you put on some shoes. Yeah.
and I looked you up or shined you up thank you how do you feel it kind of
feel like heavy at the moment and it gives me a whole different body shape
yeah I got boobs and a bum and that's really 3d molded yes it does enhance
your body shape somehow I like it but it's not my body here at the moment but
I could get used to it so I'm going to ask you the same questions I always receive how does it
feel compared to latex it's thicker and more squishy and yeah as I already told you I don't
feel the the touch on the skin as I do like wearing latex and I kind of like it but the
the sound I've heard putting it on is completely different it's more like this
swooshy sound yeah so we have some masks too I opt to try a mask yeah let's try
okay I have to warn you because silicon and hair is not a really good
combination so I put a lot of talcum powder inside but I'm going to give you
a wig cap so your hair doesn't actually touch the silicon so it doesn't get
just to get in yeah it doesn't stick to it or stuck to it and whatever okay so
we're going with this one you pick this yeah yeah we also have some other masks
the picture exists over 25 different kinds of mess and this one doesn't have
eyes but it has it has two walls one for breathing in one for breathing out you
You can attach the typical gas mask hoses.
And now let's get this off the styrofoam head.
So it's really really stretchy as you can see.
You can pull it out.
Not that easy but...
So you're going to put it on the chin and I'll pull it across your head.
So teamwork, yeah?
Like the electric mask. Here we go.
Oh!
That worked pretty good actually. Let me check. How does it, is it like, is it okay?
I can't see a thing. Yeah, you couldn't see a thing because there are no eye heels.
But if you can talk we can hear you. Yeah. Yeah. So how does it feel? I never went dying but it
kind of feels like a scuba mast. So it's kind of heavy but yeah I can breathe in, I can breathe out
so it's still comfortable okay do you want to turn around like i can grab your shoulders and
turn you around so you don't fall no safety concerns here okay
so you can't see a thing but breathing is okay yeah it's fine it's totally fine it looks so
cute with the like the whatever it is ears horns i don't know it's really cute i also like the color
and i also love the whole look with the cats here together shame you can't see it yourself
Well, I can show you some pictures afterwards.
So is it comfortable?
Yeah, it is for sure.
Okay.
I have a lot of space in here.
It's more space than I usually have in latex masks.
So yeah, it's okay.
I think my makeup will still be fine after it.
That's good to hear.
It's important for us girls.
So yeah.
you can brush it out and then you look fresh again yeah it's fine yeah better
than too much lube yeah with the hair well I see what you you told me about
the stickiness yeah where's the wig cap is it inside yeah I think so oh we kept
we lost the wig cap inside. Okay we put the wig cap on again because you're going to put on the
second one and I want you to see yourself with the mask so we're going with this one. The kitty cat.
The kitty cat. Like once again.
Alright he looks super cute with the lashes and that you can see the eyes. I think it's nice. I
I think I like this one better. I like the kitty cat look. Yeah. I love it.
I can like detach the mouthpiece. Oh wow. Wait a sec.
So there you go. Now you can actually talk and... It kind of looks like the Catwoman. Yeah it does.
it does i love it now it looks great cute i'm not a huge fan of pink but i still love the mask
it's cute and it feels super comfortable it's comfortable yeah for sure it's tighter than the
other one okay it's still comfortable you have also like a hair bun here but that's okay the
next time i have to put it down too but yeah it's still nice fine yeah love it super squishy and
the ears are you what do you prefer i think i prefer this one because i like seeing your eyes
with or without the mask with the mouthpiece oh wow yeah so don't talk that much yeah you can
I can still talk but it gives more like a more like a whole look
with the pink one?
yeah with the without that much skin so yeah
I think I prefer this I haven't seen the other one
so I prefer the one without the mouthpiece
yeah
and I really like the Catwoman look
Catwoman look?
yeah
since you
nice
with the nails
yeah
I mean Futura X does have some gloves also with the silicone nails but with your long fingernails
so we opted for no gloves here but you can check out the homepage and have a look yourself
anyway I'm glad you joined me today thank you it was a lot of fun
it's a quite new experience yeah I loved it you loved it yeah oh wow
I'm so glad because otherwise what would I do if you hated it?
Thank you so much for having me again.
I love you here so you're always welcome to join me.
Thank you.
I always get a question how do you get out of it or don't you get stuck in it?
And I think you don't get stuck in it because you put a lot of grief inside.
I have no clue. So I'm quite curious about this question too.
About the answer.
I think you can just simply put it on shoulders like every make-up you can see
but I'm going to take you to the shower and you can undress under the shower
because I think that's the easiest way to just get under the shower and use the
water to pull the silicon away from your skin okay and then undress.
So, we will see you in a second.
Yeah. Anyway, thanks for joining today and give the video a thumbs up. Check out her Patreon and her socials.
I'll link everything down below the video.
And I hope you enjoyed it.
I hope to see you again soon. It's been a while.
Anyway, have a nice day.
See you next time.
Bye.